One key to knowing how a try block functions is
understanding which other blocks run based on what
happens in the try block. For starters, the try
block will return a divide by zero error because
games is set to 0, and one cannot divide by
zero. For this reason, the except block runs as a
runtime error has occurred. The else block runs if
the try block produces no errors, so it will not
run in this case. Lastly, the finally block runs
regardless of what the try block produces. Thus,
the try, except, and finally blocks run in this
case, and I will run this code to prove this
point. The second question asked what would happen
if we changed the games variable value to 2. This
time, the try block does not produce an error, so
the except block does not run, but the else block
does run, as it will always run when the code in
the try block does not produce any errors. And the
finally block, again, runs regardless of the try
block results. Thus, in the second example of this
code, the, try, else, and finally blocks run, and
I will run this code to prove those results. One
final note: while the try block's main aim is to
run code that might raise an exception, it doesn't
return an error. Rather, it raises an error or
allows one to be propagated. So, you might want to
use raises instead of returns when talking about
errors emerging from a try block for clarity.